vipjatt.com 2014-06-18

# 

This Privacy Policy explains how mPlay.fm collects and utilizes your personal information when you use our products and services. Details regarding specific topics may be found via the topic index below.

WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?

mPlay.fm collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services, communicate with you about those products and services, and provide effective, timely customer support when needed. We will never rent or sell any of the personally-identifiable information we collect from you to third parties, and will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent, unless such sharing is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

To access some of our features like SmartLists, liked songs, playlist & albums etc. You must open an account or complete an online registration with mPlay.fm. Information gathered during the registration or account creation process, or during access to particular products and services, may differ based on the nature of the product or service. Information that you provide when registering or creating an account, or accessing or using your account or the mPlay.fm products or services associated with your account, may include: name, gender and email address; information concerning software downloaded.

We will not sell, rent or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as set forth below.

HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

mPlay.fm understands that it is a privilege to have you as a customer and is committed to protecting your personal information. We use the following controls to protect your personal information:

Use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information;

Use of encryption for sensitive personal information, such as user passwords;

Restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who do; and

Bind subcontractors with contractual, technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information.

WHEN AND HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?

mPlay.fm does not use your personal information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. mPlay.fm does not sell, rent, or share your personal information to a third party unless you consent to provide such information to a third party partner or content service.

Also, mPlay.fm may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law; (b) comply with the order of a competent judicial authority in any jurisdiction; (c) comply with legal process served on mPlay.fm; (d) protect and defend the rights or property of mPlay.fm; or (e) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of mPlay.fm products or the public at large.

MusicDilSe Websites and products contain links to other Websites and products. MusicDilse is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites or products. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices.

TELL FRIENDS

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend or friends about our app, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email invitation to visit the app. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending these emails. The friend may get the App Store link to download the app.

THIRD PARTY AND GOOGLE ADSENSE ADVERTISING

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our app. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We use Google Adsense as one of our advertising Ad networks. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with mPlay.fm products, services and Web pages. "Updated" may be used to alert users to recent changes and to the date of the last update. We also post FAQ's from time to time on specific products.

NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE

We customarily release alpha and beta versions of our products, which are further refined before the release of the final "Gold" version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our products generally, in all stages of release. mPlay.fm does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. mPlay.fm shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the United States.

CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our products or services or would like to make a complaint, please contact:

Music.vipjatt.com@gmail.com
